How much time do we have?
Uh, t-minus five hours,
37 minutes
To onset of meteor shower.
Okay, our position
is 34.48 degrees north,
118.31 west.
That means the azimuth
Should be...
168.22 degrees relative
to magnetic north
With an elevation
of 49.93.
Anything yet?
Uh, we have a signal,
but there's no frame lock.
Ha. How about now?
- We did it.
We have the west
coast feed of HBO.
Ooh, Real Sex.
Big deal. Every time
I watch that show
All right, let's see
what's on the east coast feed.
Oh, hey. Dune.
Not a great movie,
But look
at that beautiful desert.
Too bad Sheldon
couldn't come with us.
Oh it's just not the same without him.
Oh, this sucks
I'm switching back to Real Sex.
Sheldon's log.
star date 63345.3
While my colleagues are off
Observing the Leonid
meteor shower,
I have remained behind
to complete my paper
On the decays of highly excited
massive string states.
Although my research is going well
I do miss the warmth of human companionship.
Hahaha.
And good evening to you,
Siam Palace.
This is Sheldon Cooper.
Yeah, I'm going to be
dining alone this evening,
So I'll be reducing
my usual order.
I'd like to start
with one quarter
Of the assorted appetizers plate
And, uh, one half
of the golden treasure for two.
Oh, for heaven's sake
In the mid-18th century,
King Rama IV of Siam
divided a huge empire
Amongst the colonial powers
of Europe
In order to preserve his throne.
Surely, you,
his cultural descendant,
Can handle pad Thai
and dumplings.
Sheldon help!
I need to go--
but you keep in mind
That my sharply worded comments
On yelp.Com recently took down
a local muffin store.
Penny. Penny. Penny.
Come in! Hurry!
Penny?
I'm back here.
Penny. Penny. Penny.
Oh, for god's sakes,
I'm in the bathroom!
Shall I come back
at a better time?
Get in here! Hurry!
Don't you dare knock.
Hello.
I slipped in the shower,
And I think I dislocated my shoulder.
Not surprising.
You have no safety mat
or adhesive stickers
To allow for purchase on a surface
With a low coefficient
of static friction.
What?
Tubs are slippery.
I know. I slipped.
I have a series
of whimsical duck stickers
On the bottom of my tub.
Yeah, okay, whatever.
Will you just turn the water off
and help me up?
They're holding
umbrellas.
what?
The ducks in my tub.
Uh-huh.
They're whimsical because ducks
have neither the need for
Nor the ability to use umbrellas.
Oh, my god. I got to go
to the emergency room.
Well, assuming you're correct
that your right humerus
Is no longer seated
in the glenoid socket,
I would certainly think so.
Okay, can you drive me?
I don't drive.
Well, I can't drive!
Well, it seems we've reached
an impasse.
Ow.
I could call you a cab
or an ambulance.
No, no, no.
I can't wait that long.
You got to help me, please.
All right. Let it never be said
that Sheldon Lee Cooper
Ignored the pleas
of a damsel in distress.
No one's saying that.
Let's go.
Well, it does seem rather ironic
That for want
of 99-cent adhesive ducks,
We both might die
in a fiery car crash.
I wish Penny didn't for want
didn't have to work.
She loves camping.
Yeah, that would
have been great.
You and Penny having sex
in the tent
While I sit out here
and watch Howard hump a cactus.
Okay, the best I can tell,
There are eight other
camp-sites nearby.
Mostly science nerds like us,
But just over yon
ridge are two
Not unattractive
middle school teachers
Who reek of desperation.
Wow. Wonderful.
How old are they?
Oh I don't know. 50, 55.
Oh, menopause.
Nature's birth control.
Come on.
You guys can't be that hard up.
I am.
Yeah, me, too.
Look-- they gave me home-made cookies
of course, they did.
That's what grandmothers do.
So, what are we waiting for?
Relax.
I said we'd stop by
a little later
After they have their nap.
Good idea.
They'll be refreshed.
Cookie?
Yeah. Thank you.
Not bad.
Yeah, very tasty.
Well, so tell me more
about these teachers.
Not much to tell.
They had a VW Microbus
And were wearing tie-dyed
Grateful Dead shirts.
Huh.
Mmm.
Good cookies.
I see no organizational
system in here whatsoever.
Which panties do you
wear on Mondays?
I don't need panties.
I just need shorts
and a shirt.
My mother always told me one
should wear clean underpants
In case one is in an accident.
One was already in an accident.
That doesn't mean one
won't be in another,
Especially if I'm driving.
Clothes, Sheldon.
I need clothes!
Okay.
Here.
Seriously?
Those shorts with that top?
All right.
No.
Oh, that's cute.
We should have you checked
for a concussion.
okay.
Now, you got to help me
put these on.
All right.
But don't look.
Don't look?
I don't want you
to see me naked.
Oh.
Well, that's understandable.
You may be interested to know
that a prohibition against looking
Is well established
in heroic mythology.
Uh, Lot and his wife,
Perseus and Medusa,
Orpheus and Eurydi...
Yeah, great.
They always look.
It never ends well.
Ok, now you gotta help me get my arm
into the sleeve.
Ok.
Is that my arm?
It doesn't feel
like an arm.
Then, maybe you
should let it go.
All righty.
Stars are pretty, aren't they?
Up above the world so high,
Like little diamonds in the sky.
That's beautiful, dude.
You should...
You should write that down
Before someone steals it.
- So, when do the meteors get here?
- The meteors don't get here.
The earth is moving
into their path.
I can feel it.
I can feel
the earth moving.
It's moving too fast.
Raj, slow it down.
Okay, how's that?
Better. Thanks.
Stars are pretty,
aren't they?
What's so funny?
It's your American accent.
Everything you say
sounds stupid.
"stars are pretty, aren't they?"
For the record, I
should let you know
This is my first time driving
an actual motor vehicle.
You have your
learner's permit, right?
Yes, and I have logged
A considerable number of hours
on a simulator.
- Good.
- Didn't work out well.
All right,
can we please go?
One moment.
According to my driver's ed book,
a side mirror is properly adjusted
When a portion of the is
driver's door handle
Is visible in the
lower right corner.
There's the handle.
Oh, no, too far.
Bringing it back.
Optimized.
Now, where is the switch
To adjust
the passenger side mirror?
It's right there.
Where is the passenger
side mirror?
In a parking lot in Hollywood.
- Now, can we please go?
- Yes. As soon as I adjust my seat.
Whee!
Oh, dear.
I'm going to have
start again.
If I could speak
the language of rabbits,
They would be amazed,
and I would be their king.
I hate my name.
It has "nerd" in it.
Len-nerd.
I lost my virginity
to my cousin Jeanie.
I would be kind
to my rabbit subjects.
At first.
You know what's a cool name?
Angelo.
That has angel and jell-o in it.
It was my Uncle Murray's
funeral.
We were all back
at my Aunt Barbara's house.
Our eyes locked
over the pickled herring.
We never meant for it to happen.
One day, I hold a great ball
for the President of France,
But the rabbits--
they hate me and don't come.
I am embarrassed, so I eat
all the lettuce in the world
And make them watch.
People could call me Angie.
Yo, Angie, how's it goin'?
To this day, I can't look at pickled herring
without being aroused. That is a shame.
oh! Cousin Jeanie.
Could you please drive
a little faster?
Oh, I think we're going
sufficiently fast.
What's that?
Nothing. The engine does that
sometimes.
It can't be nothing.
The check engine light is on.
We need
to find a service station.
No. The light has been on
since I bought the car.
All the more reason
To consult with a mechanic
before it explodes.
It's not going to explode.
Just keep driving.
Warp speed ahead, Mr. Spock.
Mr. Spock did not pilot
the Enterprise.
He was the science officer,
and I guarantee you that
If he ever saw the Enterprise's
check engine light blinking,
He would pull the ship over
immediately.
Oh, god, I'm gonna lose the arm.
Oh, oh, red light.
Release accelerator
And slowly apply...
the... brake.
Nailed it.
While we have a moment,
may I ask you a question?
What?
Why do you have the
Chinese character for soup
Tattooed on your
right buttock?
It's not soup.
It's courage.
No, it isn't.
But I suppose
it does take courage
To demonstrate that kind
of commitment to soup.
How did you see it?
You said you wouldn't look.
Sorry.
As I told you, the
hero always peeks.
Anything?
No. That was the last
pudding cup.
No!
What about Slim Jim's?
That's what he used to eat his pudding, remember?
Right! That was so good!
Sweety and meaty
at the same time.
Wait. Wait, wait.
So you're saying
We're out of food?
The only thing in here
are blue ice packs.
I know they're poison,
But they look like big,
yummy otter pops.
Oh, god, I am so hungry.
Me, too.
Check and see
if we have any more pudding.
All right, there's no need
to bark at me.
According to the inexplicably
irritable nurse behind the desk,
You'll be seen after the man
who claims
to be having a heart attack,
But appears to be well enough
To play Doodle Jump
on his iphone.
We have to fill these out.
"describe illness or injury."
I dislocated
my shoulder.
All right.
And how did the accident occur?
You ready know that.
"cause of accident."
"lack of adhesive ducks."
Okay, medical history.
"Have you ever been diagnosed
with diabetes?"
No.
Kidney disease?
Migraines?
Getting one.
"Are you currently
pregnant?"
no.
Are you sure?
You look a bit puffy.
Change migraine to yes.
"When was your last
menstrual period?"
Oh. Next question.
I'll put, "in progress."
Okay, moving
to psychiatric disorders.
"list all major
behavioural diagnoses,
"e.g. Depression,
anxiety, etcetera."
Oh, my god, what the
hell does this have
to do with my
stupid shoulder?!
"episodes of sub psychotic
rage."
Ass.
"possible tourette's."
All right. "moles, lesions
or other skin conditions."
"soup tattoo on right buttock."
Hey, Sheldon,
Sheldon, look,
I am scared and
in a lot of pain.
Could you please just take a
break from being you and try being--
I don't know--
comforting?
I'm sorry.
There, there.
Every thing's going
to be fine.
Sheldon's here.
Thanks.
That's much better.
Oh, I'm so hungry!
Will you shut up?
We're all hungry.
Okay, our objective is
The boy scout
camp-site to the east.
Easy target.
Big doughy scout master,
couple of cubs, most webelos.
What kind of score
we looking at?
Hot dogs, buns, s'mores.
I mean, it's a freaking 7-11.
All right,
Everyone grab flash lights.
Oh, my god, could it be?
Yes!
My mother put an "I love you"
brisket in my backpack.
Quick, get forks.
You don't need forks.
It's so tender,
it falls apart in your hands.
He's right.
I feel like we're forgetting
something important.
Me, too.
But what?
Maybe a Tupperware bowl
of roasted potatoes and carrots?
Yes!
Now remember, you were given
powerful pain medication
And a muscle relaxer,
So, uh, don't operate
heavy machinery.
Try not to choke
on your own drool.
Wait. You have
To help me get into bed.
Sheldon has to get me into bed.
Bet you never thought
I'd say that.
Yes.
The charm of your drug addled
candour knows no bounds.
You know, people think
you're this weird robot man
Who's so annoying all the time,
and you totally are.
But then it's like that movie
Wall-e at the end.
You're so full of love,
And you can save a plant
And get fat people
out of the floaty chairs.
That's a fairly laboured metaphor,
but I appreciate the sentiment behind it.
Sing "Soft Kitty" to me.
"Soft Kitty" is for
when you're sick.
You're not sick.
Injured and drugged
is a kind of sick.
soft kitty, warm kitty,
little ball of fur...
Wait, wait.
Let's sing it as a round.
I'll start.
soft kitty, warm kitty,
little ball of fur...
I'll start over.
soft kitty, warm kitty, little ball of fur
Soft kitty, warm kitty, little ball of fur.
soft kitty, warm kitty,
little ball of fur...
happy kitty,
sleepy kitty
purr, purr, purr
purr, purr, purr.
...And the next morning
when he woke up,
He rolled over and realized...
duh-duh-duh!
...She was his cousin.
That's still not funny.
And she was my second cousin.
And she was my
second cousin.
You're a real douche.
Who cares?
You slept with your cousin.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net